There's the real world and there's the virtual world and more and more in the
future you will go in between those constantly and we want to dress people
in both worlds. When we decided to start Atta Kack three years ago at that same
time we came across Clow and realized that what I've been doing for ten years
prior that physically draping fabrics on live models that's now possible to do
digitally to a very large extent. When we start the design process and do it
digitally we're ending up with a digital product which then makes it possible
to do it digitally. When we start the design process and do it digitally we're ending up with a digital product which then makes it possible to
both like can present it immediately instantly. So for us we the same day we
have designed something we can actually start to sell it in an online store or
we can post the design process in social media to show what we do and see if we
get any feedback of it. Today Atta Kack works as both a fashion brand and a
fashion consultancy studio where we have the possibility of trying different
potential solutions that the 3d technology gives us both in a
small-scale brand and with larger enterprises. That's part of our vision to
like inspire other brands to digitize themselves it's a very creative way of
working. Our aim for Atta Kack is to be the world's most relevant fashion
brand and working with 3d visualization is the central part of that. Yeah maybe
in the future we will sell more virtual garments than physical ones.
It's a very fun time with so many possibilities. Feels like endless now. We
have lists of ideas we just want to do.
We use the 3d tools to create our own designs.
And the 3d tools include everything from styling to grading to design
development to animation to fittings. It really affects all stages of what we're
doing.